American Civil Liberties Union Records: Subgroup 2, Organizational Matters Series, 1947-1995: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Special Collections.
- Series 1: Organizational Matters, 1930-1995; 582 boxes
  - Subseries 1E.10: Departments: Public Information and Education Office, 1948-1988; 23 boxes
    - Supreme Court: "The Return of the Monarchists" Askin and Pollitt, 1988; 1 folder (Box 371, Folder 11)
    - Trageser v. Libbie Rehabilitation Center, 1978; 1 folder (Box 371, Folder 12)
    - Voter Registration Project, 1984; 1 folder (Box 371, Folder 13)
    - Voting Rights Act, 1981; 1986; 1 folder (Box 371, Folder 14)
    - Walker, Samuel: Miscellaneous Papers, undated; 1 folder (Box 371, Folder 15)
    - Walker, Samuel: Response to Donahue, William A. re: "The Politics, 1984; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 1)
    - Washington Office: Legislative Issues, 1975-1980; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 2)
    - Washington Office: Memoranda, Press Releases, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 3)
    - Washington Office: Press Release, Correspondence, 1981-1986; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 4)
    - Washington Office: Statements, Correspondence, 1981-1986; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 5)
    - White v. New Hampshire Dept. of Employment Security, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 6)
    - Winters v. City of Klamath Falls, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 7)
    - Wilder v. Bernstein, undated; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 8)
    - Wiretapping, 1976; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 9)
    - "With Liberty and Justice for Women" Report, 1982; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 10)
    - Wolman v. Rostker: Social Security Numbers and the Draft, 1980; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 11)
    - Worthy, William: Correspondence, 1982; 1 folder (Box 372, Folder 12)
    - Affiliate File, 1974-1988; 6 boxes
      - Alabama, 1976; 1 folder (Box 373, Folder 1)
      - Arizona, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 373, Folder 2)
      - Connecticut Civil Liberties Union, 1975-1984; 1 folder (Box 373, Folder 3)
      - Georgia, undated; 1 folder (Box 373, Folder 4)
      - Hawaii, undated; 1 folder (Box 373, Folder 5)
      - Idaho, undated; 1 folder (Box 373, Folder 6)
      - Illinois, 1975-1986; 2 folders (Box 373, Folder 7-8)
      - Illinois: Annual Report, Press Clippings, 1984-1985; 1 folder (Box 373, Folder 9)
      - Indiana, undated; 1 folder (Box 373, Folder 10)
      - Kansas, undated; 1 folder (Box 373, Folder 11)
      - Iowa, undated; 1 folder (Box 373, Folder 12)
      - Kentucky, undated; 1 folder (Box 374, Folder 1)
      - Louisiana, 1977-1987; 1 folder (Box 374, Folder 2)
      - Maine, undated; 1 folder (Box 374, Folder 3)
      - Maryland, undated; 1 folder (Box 374, Folder 4)
      - Massachusetts, undated; 1 folder (Box 374, Folder 5)
      - Michigan, undated; 1 folder (Box 374, Folder 6)
      - Minnesota, 1976-1986; 1 folder (Box 374, Folder 7)
      - Mississippi, undated; 1 folder (Box 374, Folder 8)
      - Missouri, Eastern, 1975-1987; 1 folder (Box 374, Folder 9)
      - Missouri, Eastern: ACLU Report on Civil Rights Liberties, 1978; 1 folder (Box 375, Folder 1)
      - Montana, 1983-1984; 1 folder (Box 375, Folder 2)
      - National Capital Area (Washington, D.C.), 1976-1985; 1 folder (Box 375, Folder 3)
      - Nebraska, 1976-1984; 1 folder (Box 375, Folder 4)
      - New Jersey, 1979-1987; 1 folder (Box 375, Folder 5)
      - New Mexico, 1975-1983; 1 folder (Box 375, Folder 6)
      - New York, 1977-1985; 2 folders (Box 375, Folder 7-8)
      - Nevada, 1976-1987; 1 folder (Box 375, Folder 9)
      - New Hampshire, 1976-1981; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 1)
      - North Carolina, 1975-1985; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 2)
      - Ohio, 1976-1984; 2 folders (Box 376, Folder 3-4)
      - Oklahoma, undated; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 5)
      - Oregon, 1977-1986; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 6)
      - Pennsylvania, undated; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 7)
      - Rhode Island, undated; 1 folder (Box 376, Folder 8)
      - South Carolina, undated; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 1)
      - Tennessee, undated; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 2)
      - Texas, undated; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 3)
      - Texas: Press Clippings, 1984-1987; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 4)
      - Vermont, 1975-1988; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 5)
      - Utah, undated; 1 folder (Box 377, Folder 6)
      - Virginia, undated; 2 folders (Box 377, Folder 7-8)
      - Washington, 1976-1987; 2 folders (Box 378, Folder 1-2)
      - West Virginia, undated; 1 folder (Box 378, Folder 3)
      - Wisconsin, undated; 1 folder (Box 378, Folder 4)
      - Wyoming, undated; 1 folder (Box 378, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 1F: The Roger N. Baldwin and American Civil Liberties Union Foundation, 1965-1993; 12 boxes
    The Roger N. Baldwin Foundation was incorporated in 1967 in order to raise funds to expand the ACLU's litigation work, with the foundation's directors drawn from the ACLU's National Board. Original Foundation plans called for six areas of Foundation work but the majority of funds were used by the Lawyers Constitutional Defense Committee (LCDC) and Operation Southern Justice, with the protection of the rights of migrant workers in California also gaining some assistance from the Foundation. The Lawyers Constitutional Defense Committee focused on defending Southern civil rights workers and had been operational since 1964.
    Operation Southern Justice originated in the ACLU Southern Regional office under the direction of Charles Morgan, Jr. and attacked institutionalized Southern racism focusing on voting rights and the Southern justice system. In 1969, the Roger Baldwin Foundation was renamed the ACLU Foundation, bringing with it a renewed interest in expanding the ACLU's litigation work. The early 1970s saw the emergence of various litigation projects under the arm of the Foundation. The aim of the projects is to provide knowledge in particular fields of litigation at the national office and to aid and coordinate nationwide efforts in major areas of civil liberties concern. Most of the litigation took place with volunteer attorneys at the affiliate level. The projects have changed over the years with current litigation projects based in New York being the Children's Rights Project, Immigrants' Rights Project, Lesbian and Gay Rights/AIDS Project, Reproductive Freedom Project, and the Women's Rights Project. Legislative Projects based in Washington, D.C. include the Arts Censorship Project, Capital Punishment Project, Center for National Security Studies/Security Litigation Project, National Prison Project, Privacy and Technology Project, and the Reproductive Freedom Project. The Voting Rights Project is based in the Atlanta Regional Office.
    This subseries (5.04 linear feet) is divided into three groups: administrative; project proposals; and dockets and reports. The administrative records, arranged alphabetically, include minutes of Foundation Board meetings, reports on financial matters, correspondence to and from Board members, documents from the 1978 National Convocation on Free Speech, and miscellaneous materials. Most information on projects in this period is contained in letters from members working on individual projects. The correspondence also reflects the relative uncertainty of the precise role of the Foundation.
    The Project Proposal files, arranged by year and then alphabetically, contain proposals for those that received funding and those that were declined. Project Dockets and Reports, arranged by year and then alphabetically, discuss significant legal decisions relating to projects and their review impact. Project legal dockets contain individual brief summarization of all pertinent project litigation cases. Most of the project dockets accompany project reports starting in 1972. The longstanding Foundation projects (started in the mid 1970s) are the Juvenile Rights Project (later the Children's Rights Project), South Texas Project, Women's Rights Project, Reproductive Freedom Project, and the National Prison Project. In addition to giving the standard report information, the National Prison Project reports extend to include numerous newspaper articles relating to the project. Projects started in the late 1980s include the Lesbian and Gay Rights/AIDS Project, and Immigrants' Rights Project.
    - Administrative Files, 1965-1990; portion of 3 boxes
      - By-Laws, 1967; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 1)
      - Certificate of Incorporation, 1967; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1967; 3 folders (Box 379, Folder 3-5)
      - Correspondence: Board of Directors, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, 1968-1972; 7 folders (Box 379, Folder 7-13)
      - Correspondence: Move to Washington, D.C., 1978; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence: Financial Matters, 1980; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence: Special Funds Sharing Agreement, 1984; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence: Children's Rights and public opinion, 1988; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence: Terms and conditions of loans to affiliates, 1989; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, 1990; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 19)
      - Executive Committee, 1966; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 20)
      - Financial Matters, 1967; 1 folder (Box 379, Folder 21)
      - Financial Matters, 1968-1973; 6 folders (Box 380, Folder 1-6)
      - Financial Matters, 1975; 1 folder (Box 380, Folder 6)
      - Financial Matters: Tax Counsel, 1967-1970; 1 folder (Box 380, Folder 7)
      - Financial Matters: Tax deductible fund-raising, 1967; 1 folder (Box 380, Folder 8)
      - Financial Matters: Tax exemption application, 1969; 1 folder (Box 380, Folder 9)
      - Lawyer's Constitutional Defense Committee - Foundation merger, 1967-1969; 1 folder (Box 380, Folder 10)
      - Mailings, 1975-1975; 2 folders (Box 380, Folder 11-12)
      - Minutes, 1965-1980; 6 folders (Box 380, Folder 13-18)
      - Minutes, 1981-1990; 2 folders (Box 381, Folder 1-2)
      - National Convocation on Free Speech, 1978; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 3)
      - Prospectus information, 1967; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 4)
      - Request for support, 1978; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 5)
      - Transition, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 6)
    - Project Proposals Files, 1967-1987; portion of 2 boxes
      - Create a Bill of Rights for the Disinherited, 1967; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 7)
      - Juvenile Court, 1967; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 8)
      - Mental Ill, 1967; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 9)
      - Operation Southern Justice, 1967; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 10)
      - Selective Service, Conscientious Objector, 1967; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 11)
      - Untied Farm Workers Organizing Committee Legal Services, 1967; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 12)
      - Emergency Justice, 1968; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 13)
      - Ghetto Offices, 1968; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 14)
      - Illinois Ghetto, 1968; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 15)
      - Law and Order, 1968; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 16)
      - New Jersey Voter Registration Drive, 1968; 1 folder (Box 381, Folder 17)
      - Office of Economic Opportunity: Miscellaneous, 1968; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 1)
      - Southern Justice, 1968; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 2)
      - Church-State Development in Michigan, 1969; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 3)
      - The Condition of our Liberties, An Investigation- Action, 1969; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 4)
      - The Defense and Extension of Civil Liberties in the Courts, 1969; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 5)
      - Domestic Political Intelligence, 1969; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 6)
      - Marijuana and Civil Liberties, 1969; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 7)
      - Protection of Dissent, 1969; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 8)
      - Students Rights, 1969; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 9)
      - Unconstitutional Police Practices - Affecting Dissent, 1969; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 10)
      - Welfare and Civil Liberties, 1967-1969; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 11)
      - Volunteerism, 1969; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous, 1970; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 13)
      - Citizenship Education, 1970; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 14)
      - Criminal Justice, 1970; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 15)
      - New Jersey, 1970; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 16)
      - Operation Confrontation, 1970; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 17)
      - Training for Non-Violence, 1970; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 18)
      - Prisoners Civil Rights: Connecticut, 1970; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 19)
      - Institute on National Security, 1974; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 20)
      - Reproductive Freedom, 1980; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 21)
      - AIDS and Civil Liberties, 1987; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 22)
    - Project Dockets and Reports, 1967-1993; portion of 9 boxes
      - Annual Report, Foundation, 1967; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 23)
      - Project Dockets and Reports, dates not examined; extent not available
      - Annual Report, Foundation, 1968; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 24)
      - Chicago Convention report, 1968; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 25)
      - Southern Regional Office docket, 1968; 1 folder (Box 382, Folder 26)
      - National docket, 1968; 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 1)
      - Southern Regional Office, five-year report, 1969; 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 2)
      - Operation Southern Justice, description, 1969; 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 3)
      - National Capital Area docket, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 4)
      - Government Surveillance and Data Collection docket, 1972; 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 5)
      - Juvenile Rights docket, 1972; 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 6)
      - Government Data Collection prospectus, 1972; 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 7)
      - National Prison prospectus, 1972; 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 8)
      - National Prison docket, 1972; 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 9)
      - Voter Law docket, 1972; 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 10)
      - Women's Rights docket, 1972; 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 11)
      - Juvenile Rights docket, 1973; 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 12)
      - Juvenile Rights reports, 1973; 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 13)
      - Mental Health Law, summary of activities, 1973; 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 14)
      - National Prison docket, 1973; 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 15)
      - National Prison prospectus, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 16)
      - National Security and Government Secrecy docket, 1973; 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 17)
      - Southern Justice docket, 1973; 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 18)
      - Southern Office docket, 1973; 1 folder (Box 383, Folder 19)
      - Women's Rights docket, 1973; 2 folders (Box 384, Folder 1-2)
      - Juvenile Rights Docket, 1974; 1 folder (Box 384, Folder 3)
      - Mental Health Law - summary of activities, 1974; 1 folder (Box 384, Folder 4)
      - Military Rights Report, 1974; 1 folder (Box 384, Folder 5)
      - National Prison Docket, 1974; 1 folder (Box 384, Folder 6)
      - National Prison Report, 1974; 1 folder (Box 384, Folder 7)
      - Reproductive Freedom Docket, 1974; 1 folder (Box 384, Folder 8)
      - South Texas Report, 1974; 1 folder (Box 384, Folder 9)
      - Women's Rights Docket, 1974; 1 folder (Box 384, Folder 10)
      - Southern Office Docket, 1974; 1 folder (Box 384, Folder 11)
      - Southern Office Report, 1974; 1 folder (Box 384, Folder 12)
      - Amnesty, 1975; 1 folder (Box 384, Folder 13)
      - Infectious Disease Area Lawsuit case summary, 1975; 1 folder (Box 384, Folder 14)
      - Juvenile Rights Docket, 1975; 1 folder (Box 384, Folder 15)
      - Juvenile Rights Report, 1975; 1 folder (Box 384, Folder 16)
      - Mental Health Law, summary of activities, 1975; 1 folder (Box 384, Folder 17)
      - National Prison Project Report, 1975; 1 folder (Box 384, Folder 18)
      - Privacy Docket, 1975; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 1)
      - Privacy, Secrecy, Surveillance update, 1975; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 2)
      - Reproductive Freedom Report, 1975; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 3)
      - Reproductive Freedom Docket, 1975; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 4)
      - Sexual Privacy Report, 1975; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 5)
      - South Texas Report, 1975; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 6)
      - South Texas Docket, 1975; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 7)
      - Southern Office Docket, 1975; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 8)
      - Southern Office Report, 1975; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 9)
      - Southern Office Report, 1975; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 10)
      - Voter Law Docket (Southern Office), 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 11)
      - Women's Rights Report, 1975; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 12)
      - Women's Rights Dockets, 1975; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 13)
      - Intelligence Activities Control Act, 1976; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 14)
      - Juvenile Rights Docket, 1976; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 15)
      - Juvenile Rights Reports, 1976; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 16)
      - Mental Health Law, summary of activities, 1976; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 17)
      - National Military Discharge Review Report, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 18)
      - National Prison Reports, 1976; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 19)
      - National Prison Dockets, 1976; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 20)
      - Reproductive Freedom Docket, 1976; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 21)
      - Reproductive Freedom Report, 1976; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 22)
      - Selective Service Litigation, 1976; 1 folder (Box 385, Folder 23)
      - South Texas Report, 1976; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 1)
      - South Texas Docket, 1976; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 2)
      - Southern Justice Dockets, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 3)
      - Southern Office, Other Litigation Docket, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 4)
      - Women's Rights Dockets, 1976; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 5)
      - Women's Rights Reports, 1976; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 6)
      - Capital Punishment Report, 1977; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 7)
      - Juvenile Rights Docket, 1977; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 8)
      - Juvenile Rights Reports, 1977; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 9)
      - National Prison Reports, 1977; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 10)
      - Reproductive Freedom Docket, 1977; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 11)
      - South Texas Docket, 1977; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 12)
      - South Texas Reports, 1977; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 13)
      - Women's Rights Docket, 1977; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 14)
      - Women's Rights Reports, 1977; 1 folder (Box 386, Folder 15)
      - Juvenile Rights Docket, 1978; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 1)
      - Juvenile Rights Report, 1978; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 2)
      - Regional Counsel Report, 1978; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 3)
      - Reproductive Freedom Docket, 1978; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 4)
      - National Prison Reports, 1978; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 5)
      - Capital Punishment Report, 1979; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 6)
      - Military Rights Report, 1979; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 7)
      - Women's Rights Report, 1978; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 8)
      - National Prison Reports, 1979; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 9)
      - Reproductive Freedom Dockets, 1979; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 10)
      - Revenue Sharing Reports, 1979; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 11)
      - Military Discharge Review Report, 1980; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 12)
      - National Prison Reports, 1980; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 13)
      - Reproductive Freedom Docket, 1980; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 14)
      - South Texas Report, 1980; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 15)
      - Women's Rights Report, 1980; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 16)
      - Capital Punishment Report, 1981; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 17)
      - National Prison Report, 1981; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 18)
      - Revenue Sharing Report, 1981; 1 folder (Box 387, Folder 19)
      - Reproductive Freedom Dockets, 1981; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 1)
      - Reproductive Freedom Report, 1981; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 2)
      - South Texas Docket, 1981; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 3)
      - Women's Rights Reports, 1981; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 4)
      - Capital Punishment Report, 1982; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 5)
      - Children's Rights Reports, 1982; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 6)
      - National Prison Project, 1982; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 7)
      - Reproductive Freedom Docket, 1982; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 8)
      - Reproductive Freedom Report, 1982; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 9)
      - South Texas: "Ten Years of Struggling for Equal Justice for Mexican-Americans, 1982; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 10)
      - Women's Rights Reports, 1982; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 11)
      - Immigration (Alien Rights) Report, 1983; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 12)
      - National Prison Project, 1983; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 13)
      - Reproductive Freedom Docket, 1983; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 14)
      - Women's Rights Reports, 1983; 1 folder (Box 388, Folder 15)
      - National Prison Reports, 1984; 1 folder (Box 389, Folder 1)
      - Reproductive Freedom Docket, 1984; 1 folder (Box 389, Folder 2)
      - Children's Rights Report, 1985; 1 folder (Box 389, Folder 3)
      - Executive Directors Report, 1985; 1 folder (Box 389, Folder 4)
      - National Jail Docket, 1985; 1 folder (Box 389, Folder 5)
      - National Prison Reports, 1985; 1 folder (Box 389, Folder 6)
      - Reproductive Rights Reports, 1985; 1 folder (Box 389, Folder 7)
      - Women's Rights Report, 1985; 1 folder (Box 389, Folder 8)
      - Children's Rights Report, 1986; 1 folder (Box 389, Folder 9)
      - Reproductive Freedom Report, 1986; 1 folder (Box 389, Folder 10)
      - Women's Rights Report, 1986; 1 folder (Box 389, Folder 11)
      - Children's Rights Report, 1987; 1 folder (Box 389, Folder 12)
      - Immigration Docket, 1987; 1 folder (Box 389, Folder 13)
      - Lesbian and Gay Rights Report, 1987; 1 folder (Box 389, Folder 14)
      - Reproductive Freedom Docket, 1987; 1 folder (Box 389, Folder 15)
      - Reproductive Freedom Report, 1987; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 1)
      - Women's Rights Report, 1987; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 2)
      - Lesbian and Gay Rights, AIDS Report, 1988; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 3)
      - Reproductive Freedom Report, 1988; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 4)
      - Women's Rights Report, 1988; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 5)
      - Center for National Security Studies Report, 1989; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 6)
      - Children's Rights Report, 1989; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 7)
      - Reproductive Freedom Report, 1989; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 8)
      - AIDS and the Law Docket, 1990; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 9)
      - Lesbian and Gay Rights Docket, 1990; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 10)
      - Race and Poverty Cases Docket, 1990; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 11)
      - Reproductive Freedom Report, 1990; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 12)
      - Women's Rights Report, 1990; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 13)
      - AIDS Docket, 1993; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 14)
      - Lesbian and Gay Rights Docket, 1993; 1 folder (Box 390, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 1G: Regional Offices, 1953-1985; 3 boxes
    The Regional Offices subseries (1.26 linear feet) is comprised of correspondence between the Atlanta, Mountain States (Denver), and Washington D.C. offices and the National Office. Arranged chronologically by year and alphabetically within each year, the correspondence and materials from the Regional Offices functioned to keep the National Office informed on the activities at each office and to share opinions and advice concerning civil liberties issues. Included are regional reports, local clippings, memoranda, correspondence, and printed material. The researcher should also consult the ACLU Washington, D.C. Office Records (MC#190) and the ACLU Mountain States Regional Office Records (ML1995-9 and ML1995-10, currently closed).
    - Washington, D.C., 1953; 1 folder (Box 391, Folder 1)
    - Washington, D.C. Office Miscellaneous, 1959; 1 folder (Box 391, Folder 2)